{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of popular songs of different decades.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which song by Elvis was a hit in the 1950s?",
      "answers": ["Hound", "Blue", "Love"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Beatles song was a hit in the 1960s?",
      "answers": ["Hey", "Help", "Love"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by ABBA was a hit in the 1970s?",
      "answers": ["Dancing", "Winner", "Mama"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Michael Jackson was a hit in the 1980s?",
      "answers": ["Thriller", "Billie", "Bad"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Nirvana was a hit in the 1990s?",
      "answers": ["Teen", "Lithium", "Come"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Britney Spears was a hit in the 2000s?",
      "answers": ["Baby", "Oops", "Toxic"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Adele was a hit in the 2010s?",
      "answers": ["Hello", "Skyfall", "Someone"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Beyonc√© was a hit in the 2000s?",
      "answers": ["Halo", "Single", "Irreplace"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Madonna was a hit in the 1980s?",
      "answers": ["Like", "Vogue", "Holiday"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Queen was a hit in the 1970s?",
      "answers": ["Bohemian", "Champions", "Rhapsody"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by The Rolling Stones was a hit in the 1960s?",
      "answers": ["Satisfaction", "Jumpin", "Paint"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Katy Perry was a hit in the 2010s?",
      "answers": ["Firework", "Roar", "Teenage"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    }
  ]
}
